autoweb.com.au 2004-04-01

# AutoWeb - Your Online Guide to Buying and Selling New and Used Cars

AutoWeb is published by Web Publications Pty Limited (ABN 38 084 463 507) of 3/10 Floriston Rd, Boronia Victoria 3155, Australia. Web Publications Pty Limited is a subsidiary of AutoWeb Pty Limited (ABN 16 075 611 291) of the same address.

If you have concerns about your privacy while visiting our web site you may contact us as follows:

Email: [enquiries@autoweb.com.au](mailto:enquiries@autoweb.com.au)

#### Personal Information

If you use any of the services provided on our web site we may request you provide information about yourself including your name, address and details of how we can contact you. This information is generally required to enable us to effectively fulfil the service you have requested. No other personally identifiable information is collected from you without your knowledge. 

You may at any time request details of the information we have stored about you by sending a written request to the above contact address. Please allow 14 days for us to process your request. Requests relating to information which may have been archived may take longer to process.

We try to ensure that all information we retain about you is correct and up to date. If you believe any information we have stored about you is incorrect, or if your details have changed, please notify us accordingly and our records will be updated.

Web Publications Pty Ltd uses software provided by RedSheriff ([http://www.redsheriff.com.au](http://www.redsheriff.com.au/)) and its own internal software to measure and audit web site activity. The information provided to Web Publications Pty Ltd by RedSheriff is used to calculate the number of visitor's to the web site, the number of pages viewed by these visitors and how long they stay on the web site. Common entry and exit points may also be identified. 

This aggregated, non-personal information is collated by RedSheriff and provided to Web Publications Pty Ltd to assist in analysing the usage of the website. The RedSheriff data is also accessible by media organizations and research companies, for the purpose of conducting industry comparisons with other internet portals.

RedSheriff's Privacy Policy can be viewed on their [web site](http://www.redsheriff.com.au/).

#### How we use the information collected

Personally identifiable information we collect from you is used to fulfil the service you have requested from us such as a purchase or an enquiry. If the information is to be used for any other purpose this use will be clearly stated at the time we collect the information. If the information provided is not necessary to fulfil the service completion of the details will be optional.

Fulfilment of the service may require your personally identifiable information to be provided to a third party such as the provider of the service, supplier of a product or the goods carrier in the case of a purchase and Drive.com.au and the relevant car dealer in the case of new and used vehicle enquiries. We require that these parties protect your information in the same manner that we do.

#### Third Party Advertising

We use various third party ad servers including DoubleClick's DART and DoubleClick's Audience Network to display advertisements to you. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This information is provided to the Ad-Server and is used by the Ad-Server to create anonymous interest profiles. This information does not include and is never merged with personally identifiable information (such as name, address or email address) or any information that is considered sensitive or controversial or that would compromise your privacy. The Ad-Server(s') profiles may be accessed by the website and marketers to tailor site content, promotions and advertising, and to perform marketing research. Consumers can opt-out from these profiles at any time. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies visit the following pages:

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser."
